{"data":[{"question":"Although both his legs were broken on the crash, he managed to get out of the car before it exploded.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"on","c":"to get","d":"exploded","answer":"2","explain":"- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The patient recovered more rapidly than expecting.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"recovered","b":"rapidly","c":"than","d":"expecting","answer":"4","explain":"- expecting-> expected","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"As soon as the ship arrived safe at the airport, the victims were taken to hospital.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As soon as","b":"safe","c":"were taken","d":"hospital","answer":"2","explain":"- Safe-> safely","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"We would put out to sea if the weather is good.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would","b":"out","c":"to","d":"if","answer":"1","explain":"- Would-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Do not blame me if the tin-opener is break.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Do not","b":"blame","c":"if","d":"is break","answer":"4","explain":"- Is break-> is broken","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Please check in damage before signing the delivery note.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"damage","c":"signing","d":"delivery","answer":"1","explain":"- In-> on\ncheck onsomebody\/ something: to make sure that someone or something is safe, is in a satisfactory state, or is doing what they should be doing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The fact that every children has the same educational opportunities is essential.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"children","c":"educational","d":"is","answer":"2","explain":"- Children-> child","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"John did not celebrated a party until he received the offer of promotion in writing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"celebrated","b":"until","c":"promotion","d":"writing","answer":"1","explain":"- Celebrated-> celebrate","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"You can use it as length as you like, and it will not wear out.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can use","b":"as length as","c":"you like","d":"wear out","answer":"2","explain":"- As length as-> as long as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"If things go wrong, James, wherever you do, do not panic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"things","b":"go","c":"wherever","d":"panic","answer":"3","explain":"- Wherever-> whatever","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}